PERSONAL

- NameRuslan Serhiienko
- Email bruce.t1s@icloud.com

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian English (B1)



Creative Front-End Developer offering 6+ years of experience providing high-impact web solutions for diverse industry organizations. Skilled in developing and designing multiple web-based applications incorporating a range of technologies. Aspiring to combine broad background with strong technical skills to excel as a Front-End Developer.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Mar 2019 - Present

Front end Developer

StrongSD, Sumy

Worked with several projects using:

- React
- TypeScript / Flow.js
- MobX / Redux / React Hooks
- HTML / CSS
- Styled-components / Material UI / TailwindCSS / Bootstrap

Present

Front end Developer

self development

Working on 'pet' projects with:

Frontend:

- · React, React Native
- Typescript
- · Apollo Client
- Styled-components / Material UI
- Next.js

Backend:

- Node.js (express / Nest.js)
- Typescript
- · apollo-server-express
- graphql
- MySQL2
- Sequelize / Prisma

Jan 2019 - Mar 2019

Web Developer (React)

Medichi, Sumy

Markup development using: HTML/CSS, JS, React JS, Pug, JQuery.

Jul 2015 - Dec 2018

Web Developer

Freelance, Sumy

Markup development using: HTML/CSS, Sass, Less, Gulp, JS, Bootstrap, JQuery. Working in team with designers and developers.



EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS

Sep 2010 - Jul 2015

Specialists

Ukrainian state university of railway transport, Kharkiv

Nest.js

